Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Hang them.
Episode 112
Bala!
Archers!
My Sheikh!
Bala!
My Sheikh.
- Are you fine?
- Bala.
Bala.
My Sheikh, are you okay?
Fine.
Are you well?
I'm fine, my Bey.
Thank Allah.
İsmihan.
İsmihan!
Osman and his Alps
entered the dungeon.
Hurry up, come on.
Shall we help Osman Bey, my Bey?
No.
Our job is to sneak into the castle while
my Bey keeps them busy in the dungeon.
We'll not deviate from our goal.
We'll wait until it is time to
strike the heathen.
Let's go.
You have become one of the cruels.
And you will definitely pay the price.
However, who will pay the price mostly...
are the ones who stood behind you and
remained silent in front of all this injustice.
It will be difficult for them
to reckon with.
Osman Bey.
When those arrows are shot...
your hearts will be harmed.
And my Sultan Alaeddin is about to come.
I will cut off all of your heads.
And I'll wander around
the tribes with them.
That no one would dare to
betray and rebel again.
Let whoever wants come.
If one of us is going to fall
to the ground today...
...we are all ready for that.
The decision is yours, Mother Sultan.
None of you can get
out of this castle alive.
Because I still have the advantage.
Olof.
Are you still here?
I am here, Osman.
I am here to kill you.
Okay, then.
Whoever draws his bow first...
and whoever reaches his
arrow to the target first...
we are ready for it.
But what about you, İsmihan?
Tell me.
If you don't let me get out of
here with my loved ones...
we'll see...
who longs for martyrdom...
and who is afraid of death
Now...
I'll take my Sheikh and Bala
and get out of here.
You can do this, Osman.
If you leave Mesut here...
I can forgive your rudeness.
We have the guts.
But do you have the courage?
Tell us.
Look.
Did you see any hesitation
in my Sheikh?
Look at Bala Hatun.
Did you see any suspicion
of her desire to testify?
Look at me
and look at my warriors.
Look into the eyes of those who
are not afraid of death.
Look, so that you can
remember death.
Remember death.
Your common interest that
brought you together...
are greed by force...
and the love of money...
and self love.
Soldiers.
Keep all your arrows
away from the warriors. (Alps.)
Direct them to Osman Bey
and those next to him.
The fastest is the one who kills.
Let's see.
Osman, don't compare me to your
former competitors.
You've never seen anyone like me before.
Let's see.
Hadrat Sultan Alaeddin is coming.
Have you heard?
Look at your fate.
Your death decision (death firman)
is coming
Vice Emperor Kantakuzenos is coming.
What will you do now, Osman Bey?
He has become very weak...
and his body will not bear it.
We belong to Allah and to
Him we shall return.
The dead are increasing day
by day, Kumral Abdal.
Does the treatment you
use never help?
The treatment I'm using doesn't do much
for the frail, Malhun Hatun.
And it does not
benefit the healthy ones.
It only reduces the
effect of the poison.
If I can't find the source of the
poison, I can't find the cure
This snake called İsmihan has brought poison
and antidote from a place we cannot find.
But it is clear
who brought this poison.
It's Marta.
It can't be anyone else.
She and İsmihan are always together.
Moreover, she does not appear
very often in the market.
She conducts all her business in secret.
But we will turn the tide against it.
You and Ülgen will track down Marta.
You will go to all the places she goes
and will find the source of this poison.
Come on, Ülgen.
Esma!
Check out the market well.
Find out who saw and met Marta
recently.
Your command, Malhun Hatun.
Orhan, Aladdin! Bring a stretcher
from outside.
The snake İsmihan started a war on
us by exploiting the lives of our people.
And we will look for all the ways
that lead to healing people.
We will find this antidote.
Inshallah, we will find it, Malhun Hatun.
Lower your swords.
It's up to me here.
Put down your swords, Alps.
Arrest the Alps.
Since you appeared on the scene,
things have not changed, Osman Bey.
The bows are taut and the
swords are always raised.
Is there no limit to your impudency?
There is no limit to which I abide in the place
where my Sheikh and my wife are imprisoned.
If we had not heard what you did and
had not seen it with our own eyes...
we'd be sad about your
condition, Osman Bey.
Welcome, Hadrat Sultan.
Conditions here are as you can see.
I see things clearly, Mother Sultan.
But the situation of Sheikh Edebali...
isn't good.
But the disobedience of
Osman Bey and his wife is evident.
Hadrat Sultan Alaeddin, as you said, their
guilt is clearly visible.
They committed crimes not only
against Konya, but also against Byzantium.
They will be judged first in my court.
Is the Viceroy equal to the Sultan that
you ask me for something, Kantakuzenos?
Osman Bey will be judged in my court.
- Hadrat Sultan.
- Kantakuzenos.
If you fear for your soul,
go now.
Let it be as you want it now.
But just for now.
Take your useless men with you.
A trial will be held for
Osman Bey and his wife.
Even if his guilt is proven by evidence...
we'll be holding a trial though.
Take him to the dungeon.
Hands off!
I know very well where the dungeon
is in this castle.
Because Marmaracık belongs to me.
Like all the lands
you trample in the borderlands.
It's possible that all your property will be
taken away from you after the court, Osman Bey.
Take them.
This world is mortal, my Sultan.
Mortal.
It is a mortal world for everyone.
For everyone.
İsmihan...---
Mother Sultan.
Is Osman the only person
who should be held accountable?
Bengi Hatun.
What is Olof doing here?
Olof is my brother's killer.
This is not where
we talk about that.
Come with me.
My Allah, help us.
When did your symptoms begin?
How long have you been like this?
Yesterday was the first day and today
is the second day, Kumral Abdal.
Come on, let's go inside.
Let's check your wounds first,
come on.
Let's go.
It has been spread to the
entire market.
To the sales tables.
Görklüce.
Collect everything on the
sales tables and burn it.
Determine the homes that
aren't infected.
Don't let them out.
Your command, Malhun Hatun.
Mother.
If people do not die of poison,
they will perish from hunger.
Convoys don't come.
The stores are empty.
The supplies of the Kayi tribe
will suffice us for yet another time.
The disease has not yet reached there.
We'll manage with those supplies.
Then what, my mother Malhun?
Malhun.
Ayşe.
There's nothing in Marta's shop
We turned it upside down.
We searched everywhere.
There is nothing but fabrics.
There will certainly be a track.
We will find it.
We have no other solution.
Malhun Hatun.
Malhun Hatun
Marta.
She rented a shop from a merchant.
And she put her things there.
Who is he? Did you find him?
The owner hasn't been around for a while.
No one knows his exact location.
You will find that man, Esma.
We have time until the end of the day.
You will go into every hole in the city
if you have to.
You will find that warehouse.
Your command, Malhun Hatun.
Ayşe.
Tell the Alps to get ready.
We'll go into that warehouse tonight.
Get out.
How do you do this to us, Mother Sultan?
I trusted you.
But it turns out that there is no
difference between you and Osman.
Watch out.
Bengi Hatun,
watch out.
You..
You have betrayed us.
You united with the dog Olof who
spilled my brother's blood.
As if that wasn't enough, you brought
him into our house, too.
So many things happened.
- Are you really angry about this?
- Of course!
Those dogs...
spilled my brother's blood...
and then..
hurled slander at my husband and daughter.
I almost lost my husband and my
tribe because of those dogs.
Since you united with them...
Since you did not see our pain...
and worked with them instead
of avenging us...
It is over, Mother Sultan.
Walk the road alone from now on.
I'm out.
Don't push your limits, Bengi Hatun.
Did you think you could turn
your back on me so easily?
First...
You will listen to me, your Mother Sultan.
I have nothing to listen to.
How dare you?
Shame on you.
I thought you were a smart woman.
Don't you know about politics?
How can you be a Bey's wife?
I don't understand
politics, Mother Sultan.
But there is something I know.
You and Osman are the same.
You can't equate me with
that rebellious Osman.
I am the Mother Sultan of the Seljuk state.
And I know what Olof did to
you and all the Turkmens!
I did not choose to
fight him like Osman.
I control my enemy by holding
him in my hands.
He can't take any step without my command.
I will hit a dog with the dog.
Don't you see?
Have you heard that Olof has attacked
a single tribe or a single Turk since I came?
You can't hear.
Because he can't.
And now...
In order to control
Osman with my own hands...
I need Olof.
But don't...
think I'll forget what he did
to you and your tribe.
I don't forget anything.
And when the time comes...
Olof will get his punishment.
However...
If you try to interrogate me again...
I will separate your head
from your body!
Don't, Bengi Hatun.
Now...
I will ignore that
And I am sorry for your pain.
You know I love you, Bengi Hatun.
Don't force me.
And let's burn those who burned our souls.
Are you with me now?
I'm with you, Mother Sultan.
Forgive me.
Okay, then.
Now, go to your Öktem Bey.
Explain to him what I told you.
Explain to him, so that...
he doesn't have any suspicions.
Bengi Hatun.
Mother Sultan.
What will we do, Osman?
Don't ever worry.
We'll tie these chains, with which they
tied our hands, around their necks.
Oh! Osman Bey!
Whenever i see you...
Your hands are always
inside the chains like this.
The noose will be around your neck.
Those who are on the path of truth
always have a noose around their necks.
And every time I see you...
I see you waiting for the
wolf to fall like a hyena.
Do not blame me, Osman Bey.
But..
Some will fall
so that we can rise.
Where you're going to is dark.
It's clear.
But saying so is a habit.
May your path be open.
We have faced a lot of darkness so far.
But what about you?
You will spend your life
in that darkness...
Bayındır.
You tremble so nervously.
If you continue like this...
I will tear you apart.
Take him.
Take me, of course.
I will take Osman.
Andronikos is about to recover.
I can't keep him in bed any longer.
Then kill him.
Bury him in the dirt.
He won't get up then.
No.
No, Olof.
I need strength to be a legitimate ruler.
I've been striving for
this for a long time.
Killing Andronikos is not a solution.
That power...
Is it the holy cross?
Definitely.
We will take Osman...
and he will tell us
where the cross is.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to
protect this power anymore.
Shall we try to make him live?
Until he tells us where
the cross is, Olof.
The rest is up to you.
We will take Osman.
And you will get the cross.
And I will cut his head off.
How will we take him?
Gentlemen.
Marmaracık Castle
Forgive my mother, Sheikh Edebali.
We seek forgiveness from
saints of Allah like you.
Hadrat Sultan.
The dungeon...
is a place where we nurture ourselves.
We're free everywhere we
remember Allah in our hearts.
However...
Those who remove the mention
of Allah from their hearts...
even if they think they are free...
They are always prisoners.
May Allah protect us from being
like those, Sheikh Edebali.
I want to host you.
Thank you.
But I will refuse.
Being a guest in this property...
where Osman Bey and my
daughter are prisoners...
is cruel for me.
Either you put me in dungeon too...
or let me go.
Do not be of the
oppressors, my Sultan.
Doing justice is not cruel.
Every move has a result.
But you are free, unlike your children.
You can go.
Also, Sheikh Edebali...
your grandson Aladdin...
is very smart and quick-witted.
But his father, Osman Bey...
exploits his qualities in his
own games.
Alaeddin growing up with him
is not a good thing.
Alaeddin will come with me to Konya.
I will personally take care of him.
Only Osman Bey can let that.
However...
As you're so greedy...
We have no sons to leave to you.
You should know that.
However, you ask his father anyway.
I will ask him, Edebali I will
ask him.
Don't worry.
I have many questions to ask Osman.
My Sultan.
Not my prerogative, however...
Even Sheikh Edebali is among these tricks.
He doesn't deserve your respect.
Do you think I don't
know that, Vizier?
There is something my mother
did not reckon with.
Edebali is respected in Konya, too.
I can't make my followers stand
against me.
We are observing him now.
Your command, my Sultan.
And what about Osman Bey?
He kidnapped my uncle Mesut
and wanted to dethrone me, Saveli.
His end is clear.
The court is only a formality.
His head will be cut off.
Let's see.
Allah is the greatest.
Peace and Allah's mercy be upon you.
My Allah.
Our way is your way, my Allah.
Our way is to spread your
name all over the world.
Your oppression is as beautiful
as your kindness.
My Allah.
Don't leave those who
walk in your way in dungeons.
My Allah.
On this difficult day...
Our thanks will be no less than
in our days of prosperity.
Have mercy on us.
We fight for your satisfaction.
We are fighting to honor the
world with your rules.
You know our hearts.
Protect the hearts that
beat for you, my Allah.
My Allah.
We're fighting between all
these heathens and infidels.
Don't leave us alone.
My Allah.
We have no refuge but you.
Don't leave us alone.
Don't leave us alone, my Allah.
Accept our prayer, my Allah.
Amin.
Dear Bala.
- Dear Bala.
- Dear Osman.
Since our prayers are the same,
we won't stay here, my dear.
Don't worry,
we'll get out of here.
We are here.
But what about those
on the outside?
Sons?
The palace?
What are they going
through now?
You told me about a
disease.
My Allah is everyone's Allah.
Allah will protect them too, Bala.
Our children and the people of
the palace are vigilant people.
They'll get over it,
don't worry.
Yes.
And what about us?
İsmihan and Sultan Alaeddin
are like-minded.
Sultan Alaeddin's concern
is to achieve justice.
As for İsmihan, she may have
other plans.
They want to take advantage
of our death too.
Osman Bey,
Sultan Alaeddin wants to see you.
Osman!
Come on, then.
I know.
Things got a little complicated.
It got complicated, and it got complicated
a lot.
Why did Sultan Alaeddin
make such a decision, Mother Sultan?
We've agreed that you will give me Osman.
If the opposite...
Children disobey orders
sometimes, Kantakuzenos.
They may have personal moves...
and the words carry the
meaning of rebellion...
especially when you are a Sultan.
But he is my son.
That is why I have mercy on him.
Why would I show you
the same mercy?
Are you my son?
Choose the right words, Kantakuzenos.
Have you calmed down?
It is easy to educate children.
But when you want to teach
men something...
you must threaten them with their lives.
As for Osman's life...
You are the one who will
kill him, Kantakuzenos.
If you provided us with this information from
the beginning, there'd be no need for this show.
Where and when
will I kill Osman?
If he dies in my castle...
I will be in a bad position
in front of my people.
This evening, before the court...
You will take him from dungeon.
And I'll announce that he's a
disobedient person and a fugitive.
Good.
So, I am waiting for news from you.
Do you know why I haven't
killed you yet, Osman Bey?
Because you are a coward.
You always give me a reason to kill you.
The light of Konya is almost extinguished.
Even if you try to
hide it, it is.
The light of the conquests
shines in the borders now.
And you are afraid of this.
You haven't killed me yet.
You want to do everything properly...
and you want to solve that in
the court.
Thus, the legitimacy of
your authority will not be harmed.
Men who know a lot
don't live long, Osman Bey.
This is the cause of your death.
Tomorrow, when you're judged
and beheaded...
I will take your son Aladdin
and return to Konya.
Even if I die, you cannot take
my son from me.
My homeland...
will protect my son.
While you can't stand against me...
Who can stand against me
and prevent that, Osman Bey?
Don't get this out of your mind.
The flag of Islam is above
the throne on which you sit.
Even if we fall...
one of them will definitely come and
carry that banner of Islam.
As for my son...
You cannot take my son.
But...
My son will take
many things from you.
What is the meaning of this?
We'll all see when the time comes.
We'll see, Osman Bey.
We'll see.
Take Osman Bey to the place he deserves.
To the dungeon.
Osman Bey's Palace - Yenişehir
The store has two entrances, Ayşe.
Ülgen and I will enter through
the front entrance.
You and the Alps will sneak
up from behind.
We'll catch her without scaring her.
I need that snake alive.
Orhan Bey, Aladdin Bey,
this place is entrusted to you.
Grandfather Sheikh.
- My Sheikh
- My Sheikh.
Are you okay, my
Sheikh?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, but how are you?
My Sheikh.
Malhun.
There is a disease, my Sheikh.
We will tell you later.
First, are you okay?
I'm fine, fine
Where are my mother and father, my Sheikh?
Osman Bey and Bala are
in Marmaracık Dungeon.
Sultan Alaeddin ordered that they
remain locked up until their trial.
The verdict that will be
issued by the court is known.
We can't leave my father and Bala
mother alone there, my Sheikh.
We will definitely not leave them.
We will not leave them.
My Sheikh.
Where are Boran, Cerkutay and
the rest of the Alps?
They were stationed near Marmaracık.
They will enter the castle and
take Osman Bey.
Well then, we'll take them together.
While disturbing the mind
of the snake İsmihan...
The Alps will save my Bey and Bala.
And now, the sons of Osman Bey
will rise as they deserve.
You will protect Yenişehir even if
it cost you your lives.
You both will take all
precautions regarding illness.
And you both will make judgments.
Your command, mother.
Görklüce, prepare my horse.
Marmaracık Castle
Let Kantakouzanos in silently.
I will distract the Sultan.
Mother Sultan.
My lion son.
Mashallah!
Your arrival established
order in the borders.
Osman is in our hands now.
His death warrant will be
issued by the court.
We won.
We won, my Sultan.
Thanks to your ability.
This success will be enough
to scare our enemies.
Your share is great in
this success, mother.
But when we put the rope
on Osman's neck...
the people will not remain silent.
The people will accept
that Osman is a rebel.
And they will remain silent
about his death, my Sultan.
Don't think about these issues
and tire yourself..
It's true what you say, mother.
You come from a long way.
I will prepare a beautiful table for you.
For our sultan...
Hadrat Sultan.
We'll move on quietly from here.
Ten men are enough for me.
Are my men in the castle, Avcı?
They are all inside.
Kantakuzenos.
Did your sword collide
with Osman before?
I fought with Osman several times...
and with his wife Bala.
I do not praise my enemy but
you have to be realistic.
I'm very realistic, Olof.
Very realistic.
Our primary target is not Osman.
Rather, it's his wife.
When you put the
dagger to her throat...
Osman will be in our hands.
So let's go and work this out.
The loyal soldiers of Sultan Alaeddin...
guard the corridors.
Good.
Olof will kill the soldiers for us.
Everyone will think that
Osman killed them.
Let's go.
Everyone knows that we have
kidnapped Sultan Mesut.
The verdict of the court is known, my Bey.
I don't think that Sultan
Alaeddin's intention is good.
Sultan Alaeddin wants to win
the trust of his followers.
His only goal is this
However, İsmihan will not allow this.
Isn't her concern to put the
rope around our necks, my Bey?
Is there a better
opportunity than this?
No, she can't do such a thing.
While there's still confidence in the
hearts of the people towards us...
If she tries to do that, the people
will revolt when we go to court.
İsmihan's goal is not this.
She'll not judge us before she makes us
seem bad in front of people.
Are you saying that they spread the
disease in Söğüt for this reason?
She's such a vicious snake that...
they do not hesitate to rise
up by killing innocent people.
She fights me by
exploiting the lives of the people.
What if we don't find the cure, my Bey?
We'll find it.
Malhun.
Malhun is there, she'll get over this
with Kumral Abdal.
Don't ever worry.
Inshallah.
We listen to you, what do
you want, Malhun Hatun?
I heard that you arrested Osman
Bey and Bala Hatun.
They will be judged tomorrow.
It's true what you heard.
Your husband Osman is in dungeon.
May I know why my husband Osman
is in the dungeon, my Sultan?
She asks as if she doesn't know.
You all united.
And you did things behind Konya's back.
I don't do anything
behind anyone's back, Mother Sultan.
On the contrary...
I do what I want and I
look into your eyes.
Is that why you played a game with
Bala and you stole my seal?
I don't know which seal
you are talking about.
I came here to get information regarding
the trial of Osman Bey and Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey has kidnapped my
Uncle Mesut, Malhun Hatun.
You must know the
punishment for this very well.
I certainly know, my Sultan.
That's why, if you'll excuse
me, before the court...
I want to see my husband.
You can never see him, Malhun Hatun.
Right, my Sultan?
You know how dangerous Osman Bey is.
My mother is right.
You cannot see Osman Bey
until the court date.
You heard what Sultan said.
If we don't throw you
in the dungeon now...
it's thanks to Sultan's mercy.
You all got together and did it.
And you are not innocent, Malhun Hatun.
But I will not approach you
for the sake of your sons.
Bala.
As if it wasn't enough what you've
been through all these years...
Now, you're in a dungeon.
I've a husband who's being held captive in
order not to leave me alone in the dungeon.
I'd suffer again for you, my Osman.
May Allah bless you.
Tell me.
There was a flower I brought for you.
It was purple-like.
Do you remember it? What
was its name?
Oh, yes. You used to bring
me flowers before, Osman Bey.
You were so busy with the affairs of the
state and you didn't bring me again.
Yes, yes, Bala.
But it wasn't there all the time. I'd pick
it up and bring it to you when I found it.
What was its name?
You're talking about the flower of love.
(Centaurea tchihatcheffii)
Yes, the flower of love.
The flower of love.
What are you going to do?
Will you bring it again?
When we get out of here safely...
we'll mount our horses and go to the place
where this flower is.
We'll do anything to get out of here.
We cannot leave Osman
Bey to them.
How are we going
to do that, Subasi?
We can't do anything.
You have been standing since
morning, my brothers.
There are many soldiers, what
are they doing?
Are they hanging out?
It is true what
you say, my brother.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
We have to go before
someone catches up with us.
Hurry up!
Thank you but we must help
the rest of the Alps.
Your command, my Bey.
We will save them all, Inshallah.
Let's go.
The yard was the easy part...
but it looks like this place
is going to tire us.
Brothers, be careful.
We'll take my Bey and
get out of here alive.
Inshallah.
Take your positions, brothers, take
your positions.
Boran Alp, we're
enough, we'll kill them all.
Yes, we can, however...
we make the whole castle
come to us, brother.
Save your excitement for later.
Let's take my Bey first.
Brothers.
We shouldn't wait anymore.
They are coming.
Aykut.
My brother.
Brothers.
We won't leave them around, come on.
They are coming, more are coming.
Come on, brothers. Come on.
Aykut, come on!
Are you saying we're
going out, my Bey?
We'll go out, we'll definitely go out.
We've been through a lot, this won't
defeat us, my dear Bala.
We are definitely prisoners now.
But we will be free, don't worry.
It won't be that easy.
We will race.
And the winner will bring
a gift to the other.
Aren't the flowers enough for you?
And you want a gift?
Good, it's good that you already know
that you will lose, Osman Bey.
Bala, the boys are growing up, and
meanwhile, Alaca is getting old.
In my opinion, don't trust it too much.
My Alaca defeats your horse
even when it's old.
Is that what you say?
Never worry.
I'll take that gift.
We'll see.
What are you doing here, ignoble?
Excuse me, but the only gift you
will receive today...
is death.
Enough, I don't want to shed more
brother's blood, Cerkutay.
There is nothing we can do, brother.
Boran.
Cerkutay.
Aktemur Bey.
Osman Bey.
This way!
Come on, brothers, come on.
Come on, let's catch up
with my Bey, come on.
Alçiçek.
Hold on,
we'll do the rest.
Thank you.
- Take her.
- What are you saying?
No.
Your problem is with me.
Calm down, Osman Bey.
Your wife is your bond.
- Don't touch me, put your hand away.
- Bala, Bala!
Put your hand away, put it away.
Bala.
You, you... open the dungeon!
Open.
Come on, come over here.
Leave her alone! Bala!
Bala! Bala!
Open.
And now, you will stand quietly, Osman Bey
We'll get out of here together quietly.
Otherwise..
You... you...
Release me now.
Your end is coming.
You are...
Bala, don't worry. We'll ride
our horses to the places I mentioned.
- We'll ride.
- Yeah, we'll ride.
We will ride.
The corridor is clear.
And the wolf fell into our hands, right?
The day this wolf
will tear you apart is coming.
There is no such day, Osman.
Today is your last day.
You killed all those soldiers of Sultan
and ran away.
You will be remembered as a traitor
after you die.
Osman!
Osman! Osman!
- My Osman!
- Shut up!
Bring the chests.
My Bey! My Bey!
There is no one here.
Aykurt, are you sure this is the place,
brother? There is nobody here.
This is the place, brother!
Someone is coming.
You...
Why are you never following the orders?
They were after you.
There is something wrong.
They were here.
They were here but now there is no one!
What do we do now?
How do we find our Bey?
Yenişehir
Palace of Osman Bey!
Alps! Sisters!
The future of our community
is in our hands.
We're not getting out of here
until we find a trace
Come on, search everywhere!
Search everywhere!
Look here, lift this, lift it.
It smells very bad in here, Kumral Abdal.
Take it out, come on.
Allah damn this!
What is this? What is this smell?
Don't touch it.
Go away, go away.
This is poison.
So it was confirmed.
They are the ones who have poison.
If they have poison...
...they must also have an antidote.
Why do they do something like this?
Isn't it clear? Ismahan will distribute
the antidote to the people herself.
And she will become a hero
in the eyes of the people.
Then we'll find the antidote
before they do.
But how?
We have to find a way to get Martha.
Kumral Abdal, tell us.
If this is what I think it is...
...I've found the antidote.
Oh...
Thank Allah!
Come on, come on,
we are getting out!
Let's go!
They escaped!
How could this happen?
What were all of our soldiers doing?
I told you!
I said Osman would escape!
Soldiers!
Shut up, Bayindir.
Shut up.
What shall we do now, Mother Sultan?
They can't make it out of the castle.
Let's...
They didn't run away.
They were kidnapped.
Kantakouzanos kidnapped them.
However, only we will be aware of this.
Everyone, including Sultan Alaeddin,
will think that Osman and Bala have escaped.
Wow, wow, wow.
But no one will know about this.
Did you hear me well?
Yes
Tomorrow, when the sun rises, we'll inform
everyone that Osman and Bala escaped.
Sogut.
Did they torture you a lot in the dungeon?
And my mother?
Did they hurt my mother?
Yes, she was hurt.
But every human gets hurt once in a while.
We will all be hurt, Aladdin.
But this pain will enhance us.
My sheikh.
Where are my mother and father?
They are not here, son.
Ismihan must have another plan.
They were not in the dungeon.
But don't worry.
We will find my Bey and Bala eventually.
Have a seat.
My princes!
Your mother and father are captured by
the infidels for their cause.
How fortunate you are that
you are the children of...
...a brave mother and father who suffer
for the call of the Messenger of Allah
They are attacking us from
every side, my sheikh grandfather.
We kept ignoring the pain in our hearts...
... as we were always concerned
about our community.
However...
this is becoming harder and harder,
my sheikh grandfather.
Fatima keeps asking.
I can't say anything to her.
Halime.
I'm big and I'm used to this, but...
Halima needs my mother's scent.
Oh my princes, you know
the Battle of Uhud, right?
Do you remember what happened in that war?
The army of the Messenger of Allah
was defeated at Uhud.
We had many martyrs.
Even his uncle, the lion of Allah,
Hadrat Hamza, was martyred.
The Messenger of Allah
and his army grieved greatly.
And do you know what is the verse
that Allah sent down after that?
He said in Surat Al-Imran verse 139:
Do not weaken and do not grieve, and you
will be superior if you are [true] believers.
Now, let Ismihan think that
she has defeated us with her tricks.
But we are true believers.
We dedicated our hearts to Allah.
We know we will definitely win.
And we continue to fight for Allah
wholeheartedly without falling into despair
Of course, my sheikh.
Of course, my sheikh grandfather.
And now, children...
You are the ones who will run the campaign
that will change everything.
Turgut Bey will be with you too.
How, my sheikh?
Our Shahzadas (princes)will save
Masoud before Ismihan kills him.
Orhan Bey, Aladdin Bey.
The field is now yours.
We will find Osman Bey and Bala Hatun.
And you will save Sultan Mesut.
- Of course, mother.
Bala.
Bala! Bala!
- My Osman!
- Are you okay?
I'm good. Are you fine?
Ignobles! Dogs!
They tied us up.
Don't try in vain, Osman.
Your strength is not enough for everything.
There is only one way to
get out of here, Osman.
Just tell us where the crucifix is.
So everything was for this, huh?
What did you think? Did you think I would
get you out of the court and set you free?
Tell me where the crucifix is
and I'll let you live.
Are you threatening me with death?
No.
That's why your wife is here with us.
I am threatening you with her life.
You delivered even Sultan Mesut for her.
You abandoned your dreams of
being a state just for her.
What about Andranikos and the throne?
You a man who wants to interfere with
the states nearby and empower yourself.
If you would have allowed me to
sit on the throne that day...
...we would't have to do that today.
I knew you were behind those bloody plans.
- But...
- Shut up, that's enough
I don't want to hear anything
but the location of the crucifix.
Either you say it
or bid farewell to your Bala.
Say nothing, my Osman.
We'll meet in the afterlife.
Don't say anything that
will give these ignobles power.
Have you heard?
Tell me.
Just as we are not afraid of death, we are
not afraid of each other's death either.
Death is a short amount of separation.
The meeting will be in the afterlife.
If you kill me...
...you will not get any information.
But if you kill my Hatun,
you get nothing.
You're smart enough not to do this
I know you well.
Do you know me Osman?
Do you know me?
You!
I can kill Bala for fun.
Martha.
It was you, you devil!
I'm Marta.
I'm Frig.
I will kill you now Bala.
Bala, leave her
Bala!
What are you doing, Frigg?
I don't care about that cross or anything!
I don't obey, Kantakuzenos!
And I can't calm down, Olof!
Let me go.
Frig.
Calm down.
I may stop for my darling.
Bala!
My Bala!
But Osman...
...hurry up.
Speak.
Otherwise, I will not control myself.
- I crave blood
- You vile!
No.
Your beloved partner is dying, Osman.
I will take your wounded deer from you.
This is your last chance.
Its enough!
You took my brothers, my soldiers and
everything I had!
Saga!
Eric!
Uf!
Osman!
Speak up, I will kill you
if you don't speak up.
- Speak
. - That's enough, Olof!
If he dies, we won't get any information.
Osman.
Speak Osman, speak!
Marmaracik Castle
What kind of guards are you?
How could Osman escape?
Send soldiers to search!
Find that rebel!
Mother Sultan.
Aktemur is absent too.
- Alps escaped.
- How did this happen?
Find out who did this, Bengi Hatun.
Attention, Sultan Aladdin!
What happened here?
Osman escaped with his alps, my Sultan.
Knowing his punishment, he escaped
in order not to be brought to court.
Why are you standing here?
Find him and cut his head immediately!
Your Honor, by doing this, Osman admitted
his guilt and run away from the court.
From now on he is a rebel.
That is why we must take over Yenişehir!
Speak, Osman, speak!
I'll talk, I'll talk.
I will talk.
There is a shepherd in the forest
near Uzundere.
He is from Ahis.
He has a secret sentence.
What is his sentence?
"A herb is not without smoke,
nor is a valiant without a sword...
...Osman Bey sent me...
...the knife does not sharpen its handle"
You will tell this exactly like I said.
Nice.
Osman and Bala are yours.
You can kill them however you like.
We are leaving.
We sent alps to all the places my Bey can
be taken. They're all looking for a trace.
We don't have much time, Aktemur.
We will also go and participate
in the search.
Malhun Hatun, Mother Sultan,
she is coming with her soldiers.
There is news from the shepherd,
it's time.
You get out on the road quickly.
She will suspect it if she doesn't see me.
Let me know what she wants first.
I'll catch up with you after that.
Send me news.
Come and see, Mother Sultan.
Let us understand what your problem is.
Attention, Mother Sultan!
Malhun Hatun,
I wasn't expecting to see you here.
Darling, we've waited so long
for this day, haven't we?
We get what we wait for eventually.
We'll end Osman and Bala.
Lord allowed us to do that.
We also pray to our Creator.
Our Creator accepts our prayers as well.
The prayers of the infidels
will not be accepted, Osman.
They should fight for Jesus.
Olof, will we kill
Bala in front of Osman?
Or kill Osman in front of Bala?
I will kill Osman,
and you'll kill her slowly.
I'm not that patient.
We will meet in the afterlife.
But before that, we 'll ride our horses
to those flowers first. Don'tworry.
I do not worry.
Come on.
This is finally a fair fight now.
Osman!
Bala, come on.
- Come on, quickly.
- Come on, come on.
Let's go! Let's go!
Frig!
Frig! Frig!
Get up.
Come.
Your time is over, Masut.
You will pay for the your betrayal now.
Allah is the only one who
knows who dies.
What are you waiting for?
Either you do that
or your heads will be cut with his.
Executioner, do your job!
I bear witness that there
is no god but Allah,
and I bear witness that Muhammad is
His servant and Messenger
- Oh right!
We are here, Hadrat Sultan!
Sultan Mesut, you are fine, right?
I hope you're not injured.
You came just in time.
I owe you my life again.
No problem, Hadrat Sultan.
No problem, but it's not safe here.
They'll come after you when
they hear you're not dead.
We have to leave here
as soon as possible
Okay.
Let's go.
Bala, Bala, Bala!
Come on, come on, hold on.
This way, come on, let's go.
This way.
This way, let's go.
You go there and we go there.
- Stop here.
- I can make it, Osman.
No no no, we have to stop.
- We have to stop, Bala.
- No, Osman.
No no no, we should go on.
I am fine.
Bala!
We'll stop.
Stop here, come on, let's stop here.
Sit here, Bala.
Sit here.
Bala.
Open your wound.
I am fine Osman.
- I'm fine.
- You're fine, fine.
You do not show your pain
even if you are in pain, do I not know you?
You will hold on, Bala.
Hold on.
They're coming, come on
get up, walk
Go, go, go!
They shoot arrows, Bala, watch out.
Come, come.
Let's go.
Bala!
- Come! Come!
- Osman!
Come, let's go!
Where is your runaway husband?
I should be the one who is asking,
Mother Sultan.
Aren't you the one who
captured my Bey?
You should know where he is.
Let's cut to the chase now.
Why are you here?
I will not take your permission to come
to my land.
I don't know if Malhun Hatun
told you or not.
Now, hear me out.
Your Osman Bey wanted to
dethrone Sultan Aladdin...
...and enthrone Mesut.
But he did not succeed.
He got arrested.
And now he's a runaway.
This is Osman. He proved how rebel he is.
He escaped the court again.
He is now a rebel.
He has no sovereignty over you.
When you see him,
you must tell the soldiers.
Let's talk about why I am here now.
You will collect your belongings
and leave Yenişehir.
Who are you banishing
from these lands, Hatun?
I think you couldn't hear me, Malhun Hatun.
Your Bey is a rebel.
He is a rebel.
A runaway.
What lands are you talking about?
You can't get us out of here.
Draw that sword.
Draw it and I will...
...make you rot in that dungeon. I will
make everyone here rot, including babies.
You are acting unfairly, Ismihan Sultan.
We got these lands at the cost of our bloo...
I am not taking your tribe form you.
That's enough for you.
You will return to where you came from.
I don't want to see anyone in this palace
after sunset
Bala, come on.
Hold on, my dear Bala! Hold on!
They are coming.
Come on Bala, you have to hold on.
Bala.
Osman!
I will burn you and your people alive!
Your end will be the same.
Your fire will eventually
turn you into ashes!
Come to me.
I will separate your head from your body
Your tongue is as insolent as your sword
Come see
Top
frig
come on bala; They are coming
- I'm fine
- Come on, Siri! Let's go
- Are you well?
- okay
Come on, hurry up
Let's go
stop here; In order not to scare this shepherd
Peace be upon you, dear pastor
Peace be upon you, you
are welcome
- You prefer all of my food
- Thank you
- I came here to take a trust
- Then I hear you
"A herb is not without smoke,
nor is a valiant without a sword...
...Osman Bey sent me...
...the knife does not sharpen its handle"
Hmm, you want the secret.
I carry this heavy load
by my side every single day.
But you are not dressed like
our people.
Who are you?
I am Osman Bey's Alp in Constantinople.
Do not let my clothes misguide you.
I am one of you.
My Bey does such tricks, yeah.
Wait.
- What is it?
- I am not carrying it.
I just know where it is.
It is a very heavy one.
Come with me, brother spy.
My Bala, my Bala!
Osman.
You can't escape.
Not this time.
Do you know how a wolf traps his prey?
Alps!
- Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest!
Damn it!
What's it like now?
You trapped both us and Kantakuzenos!
- Let's go, Olof, they outnumber us.
- I can't leave him! I can't!
Let's go now, Olof! Let's go.
Thank you, alps.
Thank you.
We have one job left.
Come on!
Let's go, let's go.
We'll stay here for a while.
I do not want you to stay by my side while
the executioners are after me, Turgut Bey.
My Sultan.
We wake up to death every morning.
The future of our state
depends on you.
Our lives don't matter at this point.
Everything is for the state.
You sound like Osman Bey.
But now he is in the hands of Mother Sultan
with Bala Hatun.
We will get Osman Bey
and Bala Hatun safe and sound.
Care your own life right now,
Hadrat Sultan.
Can I come, my Bey?
Come!
My Bey, Malhun Hatun is emptying
Yenisehir by the order of Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan!
I knew you wouldn't stop!
She takes advantage of my father's
absence and pressures us!
Let her.
We know how to overcome her.
Eyvallah.
Shepherd!
Isn't this taking too long?
Not at all, not at all.
It's a great relic.
Do you know what the relic is?
I know of course, it's my soul.
The soul is a very heavy load.
Both taking it and giving it, it's heavy,
Kantakuzenos!
You vile!
We came.
You are the one who delivers today,
Kantakuzenos.
We'll take your life.
You and your sordid plans, huh?
I have to get rid of you all
to end this.
Or you'll die.
Look, my brothers!
He never even thinks of his own death.
I will kill you first, you ignoble fox!
You will see what it is like to
lure a lion into a trap.
Well, what about the wolf?
Are your teeth stronger than his?
Osman.
Yes, Osman, Osman.
Olof, Olof, damn it!
The wrath of my Creator
against people like you is everlasting.
And I am the one who will end you now.
You are done.
Come and see Osman, come.
So you are calling your death, huh?
Yenişehir, Osman Bey's Palace.
Her name is not Ismihan,
her name must be the exam!
Allah bless you, Ulgen Hatun.
Am I not right?
She has been an exam we must bear with.
Damn her name.
She must die.
She will be tormented by her death, I hope.
I hope her liver comes out of her mouth!
Ulgen.
What, girl?
Can't I speak evil about an evil?
Tawbah Astaghfirullah!
(I seek forgiveness in Allah!)
Come on sons, let 's go
back to our tents.
Ayse, have you prepared everything?
We have everything ready.
We are ready.
Come on sons, come on.
Are you still here, Malhun Hatun.
You are being impatient, Bengi Hatun.
Of course I am.
The palace must be
well arranged for Mother Sultan.
It is well known that
her taste is different from yours.
She is from the state.
What about you?
How can you still stand by Ismihan while
you know she's allied with Olof?
Forget about us, but don't you feel shame
after all your martyrs?
You are not perfect either, Ayse Hatun.
If you are not embarassed after
what you've done, I am not either.
Go on, the shorter the visit is the better.
Leave so that we can take care of our work.
Bengi.
You will regret it.
You will regret it so much.
But it'll be so late.
Ayse, come on.
Come on, sons, come on
Your reign is over now.
You have brought nothing but pain
to these landsç
No, you brought the pain.
We are the ones who relieve the pain.
But I will cut off your head
and relieve your pain too.
You trusted your numbers
and stood against us.
You trusted your armies,
you underestimated us.
Your only concern is gold, colonization,
creating chaos, and gathering strength
But our concern is to
bring order to the world.
We are on the right path.
He who is on the path of truth
will always be victorious...
...while falsehood will always be defeated.
Vengeance.
They will avenge for me, Osman Bey.
We will burn your Hatuns and children and
even the bones of your dead!
We will erase you all from these lands.
No, you are the one are leaving.
You'll go to west, until the sea.
We will chase you until doomsday.
Either you will be expelled
or you will perish.
You'll see, you'll see.
You will see the death of
all your children and brothers in faith
But you won't.
- Boran!
- My Bey.
Send this to Ismihan.
Tell her this is Osman Bey's gift.
Yes my Bey.
And this is Andranikos' share.
- Give this to him
- Yes my Bey.
Bala.
My Bey, Mother Sultan expelled us
from Yenisehir.
She took over the city.
She sent Kayis to the tents.
Mother Sultan, Mother Sultan...
Okay then.
Shamil, prepare yourself, you'll
be out on the road tomorrow.
What is your order, my Bey?
You will go to Konya, you will announce
that Sultan Mesut is alive and free.
Sultan Mesut will sit on the throne.
But we must gather
the Beys and the people.
You will do whatever needs to be done.
You will convince those who
ask for money with money...
...those who seek war with war,
and those who seek peace with peace.
As you command, my Bey.
Ismihan.
We'll see.
Yes, Osman Bey.
I told you that you are not equal to me.
See, your throne is mine,
your castles are mine.
Yenisehir is mine.
Hadrat Mother Sultan, Osman must have
understood that he can't compete with you.
Of course,
just before taking his last breath.
I will establish a new order
in the border regions.
Osman's end became
a lesson for the people, my Sultan.
They saw whom they have to obey.
They saw, they saw
You were always by my side on this plan,
Bengi Hatun.
And you too, Beys.
I will never forget what you did.
You will rule the market from now on.
Oktem Bey, Bengi Hatun.
Yes, Mother Sultan.
What will happen to Kayi tribe,
Mother Sultan?
How can a headless tribe end up,
Bengi Hatun?
Osman Bey is not there anymore.
The end of the Kayi will,
of course, be in our hands.
- Can I come in, my Sultan?
- Come, Avci.
Sent by Osman Bey.
Osman!
Osman Bey is coming!
- Good news
- Osman Bey is coming.
Praise be to my Allah.
- Welcome, my Bey!
. - Welcome!
- Welcome, Osman Bey!
. - Welcome, my Bey!
O Allah.
- Kids!
- Father!
My little one.
My little one, little one.
- Father.
- Son.
- My Bey.
- Orhan.
My Bey.
Thank Allah very much
you are back safe and sound, my Bey.
Yes I am, I am.
Bala.
Welcome my Bey.
Thank you.
- My Bey!
- Kumral Abdal.
Let's go.
Here we are, at the place where
our mighty tree was planted.
We are in our tents.
We will never stop until we end the ones...
...who always wanted to end us.
Allah is the greatest!
My Sultan, I sent a messenger to the towns
where we shall camp on the road to Konya.
Are you wondering why we did not camp
in the caravanserai, Vizier?
That question is beyond me, my Sultan.
Osman's rebellion courages
the other Beys.
I will break their courage with my army
and strengthen their loyalty to me.
The enormity of your army
will silence the Beys, my Sultan.
But if we do not cut off Osman's head...
...Beys may rebel.
My mother will not stop until she cuts
off Osman and Mesut's heads.
We shall take care of the other
beys in the meantime
Shadows surrounded my eyes and heart.
I was wrong, Osman Bey.
I disappointed this sword...
...that I have been carrying for years...
...to spread justice.
I am not worthy of it.
Take my sword.
Take it so I remember where I was wrong.
Take it, Osman Bey.
Whenever the right finds its course...
...and you think I deserve it back...
...then I will get this
true friend of mine back.
The exam you failed in
ended many lives.
Never fall into headlessness again.
And don't turn your back again.
I understand now that
turning my back to you...
...was turning my back to myself.
Damn me if I turn my back again.
Let this be your last mistake.
If you deviate from our cause again...
I will not give you my hand to reach...
I will step on you and go on.
This sword is for men just like you.
Eyvallah Osman Bey.
May Allah bless our war.
Amen.
Come on, let's eat.
He will be fine, right, Kumral Abdal?
Heal comes from Allah.
He will be fine, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
In The Name of Allah Most Gracious Most Merciful
When he drinks this, the poison will vanish,
right, Komral Abdul?
I don't know if this will work or not.
But if I don't give it to him now,
he'll not make it another day.
He may die.
Be optimistic, alps.
We will do our best.
Inshallah, Kumral Abdal.
Oh my Creator, You are the healer.
Heal comes from you.
Don't let us make mistakes.
Amen.
In The Name of Allah Most Gracious Most Merciful
O Healer!
Kantakouzanos died.
What do we do now?
Will the crucifix
you put on your neck save us?
Olof.
You believed that crucifix like a fool!
You forgot our goal.
You forgot Odin.
We came here to have a land, Frigg.
And we will have one.
Whether with or without Kantakouzanos.
We must!
Otherwise, you will have lived through
this scandal in vain.
You are...
...you think I left Odin for my own good.
I did not choose Jesus for this reason.
You'll understand
why I did this when the time comes.
I will end Osman.
I will avenge for all my lost friends
when he dies.
How will you do that?
I'll take the land.
The only force here is not Kantakouzanos.
There are other friends
with whom I will agree.
Who?
You'll see.
Osman.
He is being himself!
He proved his disobedience again!
Do you know what will happen
at the end of this?
The Byzantine army will come to our lands.
Osman Bey stirred up chaos
at the borders again!
He messed up the system again!
He, who did this to Kantakuzenos...
...can do anything to us.
Is your fear greater than
your loyalty, Bayindir Bey?
I ask forgiveness from Allah,
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
I just want stability.
As you ordered...
I want our system to continue.
It doesn't happen by talking.
Will we kill Osman, Mother Sultan?
No.
We will not kill him.
We will support him.
It's time to unite.
What unity are you talking about,
Mother Sultan?
To unite with the man who
causes us terrible troubles?!
You promised me for revenge.
We'll take revenge.
And we will take everything
from Osman's hand.
Osman will have only his life.
We'll make him worse than dead.
He will see the collapse
of the entire system he established.
Our brother Konur will recover, Inshallah.
- Inshallah.
We are in our tents again.
And together again.
Praise be to Allah
who has given us tables like this.
Amen.
Praise be to Allah Almighty, who brought
us together safe and sound.
Amen.
Let's eat.
In The Name of Allah Most Gracious Most Merciful
My brother Orhan has something
to tell you, father.
Say it.
Osman Bey.
Where is the relic?
You will know...
...when you grow up.
How much more
will they grow up, Osman Bey?
These valiants...
they have done a great job.
They saved the great Sultan Mesut.
You also wonder, but you use my Beys
as an excuse, Turgut.
Say it then.
Come on.
Bala, help me with this.
So you never left it, right father?
I told you, brother,
it's always with him.
There was no way else to protect it
for all those years.
But this is not the real one.
Just in case...
I have been carrying it for a long time for
them to find it on me.
Stop the game already, Osman Bey.
There is no enemy here.
Where is the relic?
It's at my sheikh.
Only he knows where it is.
So we don't have any information
even if they threaten us to kill?
This is the best.
Even I don't know where it is.
Grandfather.
You won't reveal it, will you?
I don't know,
let me think first, Aladdin.
Oh I forgot.
Sons!
Don't go after the relic.
When the time comes
it will reveal itself.
Just like how our dream of being a state
was a secret all the time...
Now it is time to reveal the state
we will found.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com